hello everyone welcome to
game b actually i just forgot
the intro for this uh
this is our round table where we talk
about what we've been doing on our
projects
how we can uh use some help and how we
can participate in each other's projects
and today since we're also working on
each other's projects we might have a
lot to discuss about that
um so that's uh that's the general theme
ajo do you want to kind of say what
you've been up to and
uh if you add anything to my intro
sure uh not right anything that's in the
intro so i can
jump right in uh so my project is wiki
election
and conferrati they are sort of two
sides of the same coin they're both
intended to fight
misinformation in uh politics science
and news
i've been working with matush on the
prototype
um hopefully getting a new version at
some point soon so i can start to see
the sort of more interesting layer as it
is now it's just
people organizations and people's
positions at those organizations so not
not a whole lot but this layer is the
legislation
um how people voted and then some
scoring to sort of show
what the legislation might mean for
somebody's values and then over time
you can start to learn sort of trends
and you know
themes about how how people vote also
just waiting on the the new version of
that
and uh actually sounds like the part
with the
figuring out the values and the voting
on them
what was developed for that might end up
being used for a number of projects so
that's where things are up there
jubilee if you want to sorry i'm on a
different
computer and i was it just notified
something i was trying to see if i could
turn on notifications
um my project is solution raising as
well as this new
emerging thing
together that is what no no not together
also together tech of course but that's
not the mlm
yeah and the product no no that is part
of what it is but it's also like the
product that is emerging through that
and so this last week
i spent my time doing this five day
course creation course and focusing on
working through that and that is what
the mlm is becoming
into is this six this six week
course that's all it's six different
conversations right i mean i'm not
putting together an actual course
that's that's not gonna work it's about
coming together and and
doing wish obstacle and then coming
together and doing that same thing for
your health and for your relationships
and for your
uh hobbies and purpose what you actually
like what you're doing
and so i've been working that part out
and what i could most use help with
um is what i've always needed most help
with which is the admin side and the
executive functioning side
actually physically
having help getting people to the event
doing the marketing and doing the
all of the admin work that is required
like email lists and
and that kind of stuff and so if there's
someone out there who is capable of that
and willing to uh
work on this project it'll possibly pay
something in the future
excellent uh for my project
so i have tons and tons of projects uh
before i was just doing reason score
which is a tool for mass agreement
um and then i kind of got that to a
level where
i was having trouble as usual as all of
us getting people to participate
trying to figure out and a lot of times
we're trying to solve big problems so
they have so many uses it's hard to find
where to put your effort to get
participation
i did hire a contractor they've been
delayed to do some research
i just found another group that was
that's doing a debate
uh on discord so it'll be interesting to
see if i can
have them at some point if they're
interested in debating maybe at some
point they'll be wanting
to try out a new debating tool uh but
also this week
i just got off a call with adam i
actually don't know how to pronounce his
last name but he's working on
eureka the eureka game um
and we're working on designing an app
for uh
for putting his processes into kind of a
social media context
so it's converting the game to a more
long-running
uh process uh instead of a game
uh although it's still gamified so you
still get points and everything
and then we're also uh
he's going to propose a new facebook
group in game b i think soon
that'll be interesting it'll be kind of
um
invite only and then there'll be tears
to where the the people with the highest
uh quality content kind of gets grouped
together and then there's some other
stuff in that
so um but he'll be explaining that and
we'll see whether it resonates with
people
um i also worked with um vincent arena
on
i'm blinking on it right now i have so
many things going on
but i had a meeting with him and we're
going to continue oh yeah i'm sorry
so after a long talk about reason score
and debating he
his main idea is what we've been
talking about the the generic uh
batching rating system uh
so he's been working on it for over a
year he's built two or three
specifically for suspicious
specific use cases using no code tools
so he's not a developer
but he's been building them so i invited
him to join
we set up a meeting uh i will be
i think i've already shared it and
facebook and that's just for me and him
but other people are invited and then i
put out a doodle no actually i don't
think i've shared that one yet but i did
put out a doodle
for a regular repeating weekly
discussion on this
thing so if anyone uh if you search for
that on
in the game be projects group maybe i
should share that to game b
as well then hopefully we can do a
repeating conversation
and adrian if that would be something
your participation would be greatly
valued
um because
you know it might be some code that
you'll reuse
uh
yeah so those are the main projects and
then i have uh
a startup that i'm that i'm helping with
creating new
um ebook reader that that gets you
more extra content more easily accessed
so
that's kind of a secret project
that i just talked about um yeah so
doing a lot of the things
uh we can continue our conversation in
lots of ways i
when jubilee when you were sharing about
yours
uh oh no i guess you kind of answered my
question about that
but if you like we could talk about that
a little bit and then
also adrian and i could talk about
um the challenge of
combining my open source project with
his currently closed
source um project uh how that would
overlap and
and and stuff or we could save that for
the
for the other meeting so uh any other
topics people want to discuss
i'm good with with either of those i
would like to mention
that um if nothing else we sure are
multiplying projects
because between even the three of us we
went from having three projects to
having about a dozen
so yes well yes that's a bit scary
yes yes now we just need other people
that come and help with the
various projects although bentley you
are helping on
a bunch of people's yeah for various
projects which is as long as they're
multiplying your own yeah
right as long as i can uh i've
i have over extended myself and i just
bought a house so i'm going to be moving
over the next month so i'm actually
taking two weeks off
like i shut down my calendar so people
couldn't book appointments i'll still
be attending a few things but i might
miss a meeting or two
um yeah does anyone know what
a job just if i wanted like a personal
assistant for a couple hours a
week for the admin type stuff and
of course needed that cheaply how would
i
go about finding someone to do the
advent stuff
i think it's it's a virtual assistant
and you could
and i think that's the title you would
actually search for on
uh uh freelancer or
um what's the up
work up work and other sites like that
it's just virtual assistant and they'll
help you
all that usually you can get someone
from the philippines that
uh you could pay very well and
uh get the uh although they're the cost
of living is going up but
uh but yeah there's there's a lot of
ways where you can use the uh
the difference in the currencies to get
a lot of value and help someone out
there's a i feel like what i'm doing in
the world is maybe not the greatest have
someone from the phillis b
philippines philippines specifically
because of their fascist
government that might get them into
trouble right if they're creating
something
in a cooperative that is dismantling
capitalism
yeah but but there is i'm sure there's a
country that it will be more
more conducive with yeah just their
english is is pretty good so that's why
they've been a good choice for
outsourcing
yep but you have a lot of south america
too there's lots of
opportunities so
uh yes so you're is this kind of your
first
iteration is that wish and what was it
blockers
what's that obstacle yeah obstacle
meetings
and then are you thinking that that'll
be a continuous
25 a month to do that or am i mixing up
the different projects
well they change weekly so just
i i might mix them up uh the 25 per
month is always
hits once we hit 10 000 people so i'm
creating a product that people can use
for free
to see if
collective crowdsourced solutions work
for them
in their own life so wish obstacle is a
big
like 100 person meeting where people can
say what their wish is and so hopefully
and they're obstacle and hopefully
somebody has a solution for the obstacle
but especially when you're starting
small that's not going to be the case
there's going to be five of us maybe
even three of us you give what your
wishes and it's more of a
hey do we have a solution if that
happens to be in this room that's
amazing
zoom room um but more likely it'll be
something that is more like a pinterest
board more like hey these are our wishes
these are obstacles and we're trying to
overcome them together
we're trying to figure out how how we
can get closer to that
even amongst however big or small the
group is the idea is to build a
for that to be a one-time event that
hopefully is bigger and draws more
people in and we can see more of the
collective intelligence
how it shows up in the room because
that's part of what we're proving
showing uh is is doing a longer course
like that
so showing up and saying like a
personal solution raising right what
does your health look like what would
you love it to look like what is
stopping you from moving forward how
many people and resources do you need to
do that maybe we can solve it maybe we
can't right maybe it's something we need
technology for maybe it's something we
need
five people four or ten thousand people
for but figuring it out in small groups
so there isn't an expert right i'm not
giving you what will help your health
you're saying what would help your
health
and with the help of other people who
are there and creating that into a
course
that people can come be part of and then
at the end of that course they have the
option
of becoming part of whatever this
entity is that may or may not
be an mlm may or may not have that that
structure as part of it
to help with recruitment and help with
financing all of the ideas that come
out of the structure but if we can just
get to 10 000 people and people put in
each maybe we don't have an mlm
i don't know yeah
awesome do you have any topics adriel
that you want to
discuss other than what i brought up no
i think just what people have talked
about so far is fine
i think mine i'm mostly just waiting
so until that happens and even then i
think i know what
where i want to go so it's i'm good
yes so if if i so what i want to do is
create some generic
open source code that kind of started
this tour you can
name groups of entities and those
entities have
attributes and you a person
the participants in the system can
rate those attributes and in the future
version put evidence on why they rated
the attributes
that way um so the
you know so it could be politicians it
could be legislation
and then there's a relationship between
those entities right
and it's just a generic relationship it
can say anything
and it would have a certain association
of
sharing the reputation of
of this thing so if a politician
has a lot of legislation that's that's
rated roy low
on these attributes and then and then
their uh co-legislature
there they co a lot of um
well i guess they you get it through the
legislation but let's say they
um campaigned for another
uh politician then you would create the
relationship and you kind of say
what's the level of influence and all
this would be crowd sourced in some way
and built that tool and and outsourced
it
and based it as close as possible to
what mark matush is doing
radic or attic is doing uh right now
then if you chose to use that
with that do you think that there that
there's a concern on your part that
it would be too much open sourcing the
unique value proposition of your system
although even before you answer that my
challenge would be that the main thing
that you're building is the brand and
the community
and the tech may not be if you're using
open source tech it may not be that
important but
what how what are your feelings on that
is that a concern or is it not
it's not terribly concerning
um really like a lot of what
wiki election and con friday are about
are where you've got like
realistically 10 or 20 of these types of
tools sort of all
merged together with the same data set
talking about the same stuff that's
really where the magic happens
so i'm really not too worried if like
you know there's a new
control made to help figure out you know
the
um the aspects and the scoring and sort
of how that works
i have no issue if that has value being
a standalone thing
as long as it's not you know sort of
taking time
from the project that it's gone from
and complicating that that's my only
concern if that
is sort of being done on zone and just
use that as a base and especially if
it keeps being improved and working
election can
see the benefits of that then that's
totally fine by me
yeah and then so what i'd like to do is
i mean i would love to just spend time
on this but i am quickly running out of
volunteer hours or actually ran out a
long time ago
so what i was thinking is we do have a
lot of people that are interested in
this
so i think what i want to do is get a
list of everyone that's interested
and then say hey do we want to
get a pool of money to pay
you know me and radic and uh maybe even
other developers
to start putting this core piece
together um
and if that doesn't go then you know
it'll just happen slower but
um yeah so that's my that's my that's i
think that's the next step in this let's
see if
there's enough interest that people are
willing to put some money towards it
all right well do you know how much
money the fund like what that
threshold would be uh no
i uh i think any amount would be
would speed up the development because
so i guess really what is
is this acceleration so even if it's
well people if if you're talking about a
fully built
prototype or a fully built
app that adrian could reuse for his
two things and it'd be fairly easy to to
reuse
i mean i think i think we'd be building
it
the core code would be built into
um like we'd be building um
wikilection and conferrati
with the code and then it'd just be a
matter of kind of abstracting it out if
we
if we accidentally build any direct
links
so there will be value even with a
little bit
of money i guess for the people that
aren't involved in contrary stuff i need
to figure out what their value steps are
um i think for a lot of them even if we
just had a dim
had a just front end not even a back end
a demo site where you could say
you know here's the food app right that
let's or here's the company app
which is kind of what mark was talking
about doing is um
and so here's some companies and here's
their rating and here's how they compare
and here's how you'd enter stuff
then they can then put that out there
and try and start getting interest
so i guess that's probably the first
step and then in that same way
we could show what
um what wiki election would look like
with a couple of
fake politicians like you've been
wanting to do right i am wondering yeah
one of the things we have not done
in the game b space to see if it gets
crickets or not is have a crowdfunding
campaign
there's been a lot of talk about them
right like crowdfunding in order to pay
for the wiki
in order to to do things that are
actually game b
specific and i don't know if there's
much interest in that because it's like
it's already happening why put money in
when when like it's already happening
it's on all the podcasts it's
that creating something that is very
game b
from within game b that has game b
people on it
creating a crowdfunding campaign and
scene right or is it something that the
people who have been talking about game
b for a long time and do have money
are willing to put money towards and is
it something that the rest of us who
have very little money but a lot of
passion are willing to put a little bit
of money towards
i know i would put a little bit of money
towards it especially if i saw that it
was something that was
generating this is real right this is
some
tangibly moving game b forward not
game b but like actual how do we get to
an omnibus society how do we create open
source
stuff that people are actually using and
it's the foundation of a lot of
different ideas that come out of
solution raising and such
anyway i think a crowdfunding campaign
that is simple but explains it in
various ways to the various different
minds in game b could be very successful
and generate i mean i'm talking like ten
thousand dollars right to
to pay you for full-time work for
however you know i don't know how long
that is but
i don't know if that's enough right
that's why i was asking for a dollar
yeah right
or it couldn't right that could be one
person you could put that towards it
yeah i mean so yeah five or ten thousand
would get you to
a pretty decent working
app may not have all the features you
want but i think it would be
big enough to provide some value so it
would be something that could probably
be gained
if you had some bad actors but if you're
if you're just starting out because
that's that's the expensive part is
trying to get all those moderator
controls
but just the general idea of being able
to rate things and display that
is probably pretty pretty simple so yeah
that that would probably be a good
goal would be ten thousand and see what
happens because so far there's been like
nick
and people doing micro solutions right
people who are like right putting a
weekend in putting time in here or there
that is
that is fine but to dedicate somebody
towards a game b
project in a way that it's like is this
what you want give me money
i think that game b might be ready for
it it might be ready
or not and then there's crickets right
now it'd be a good experiment
right uh yeah so i was thinking i mean i
would like to do
something like patreon so there's a
recurring subscription
but outside of that i guess gofundme
would be
the best other option does anyone have
any opinions about
platforms i um
partly because of the idea of testing at
crowdfunding and are
also i don't i wouldn't put in a
recurring payment i would put in a
one-time payment
right to say okay well this is what you
know to see if we can get to the ten
thousand
but there's a re like the reoccurring
payments that like trickle in
don't seem to me to be as powerful as
the rest but maybe you know i mean if
you're getting 500
a month and you're putting in however
many hours per month towards it as
opposed to getting like right now
concentrate now it's gonna be out in six
weeks two months
yeah so i think the best platform for
that and would would be
gofundme um and then yeah
put up just put up a flat dollar amount
and say
we will and then you know say even if we
don't kind of meet our goal we'll still
kind of
uh because i i don't think there's ten
thousand dollars worth of
any idea that the game b community would
support but
it'd be interesting to see what happens
yeah just this like in between not micro
solutions that you can do in an
afternoon and not
together tech let's put in a few hundred
thousand dollars
um for the bigger vision something
that's
just that like adjacent possible like
hey
is there enough interest in this to be
able to create it or maybe you find
someone from putting that out there
who's like
actually i can dedicate my time to that
and
willing to to do the actual volunteer
work which
brings up a whole other plethora of
issues but
so uh i guess the next step in that
would be to write a pitch
for that funding campaign and then maybe
get
post it in the game be project space and
get everyone's
feedback before we actually do it and
then spread it to
game but not to the game be main
group um does it sound like a next step
yeah because that is definitely a piece
of it is not even just the funding of
game b
but the um
spreading of it right that if we if
there are 15 people who are willing to
post it on their personal facebook pages
and we like each other's right then that
already brings it better than most
crowdfunding campaigns that are starting
from nothing have
i guess theoretically i could just put
the pitch in the gofundme
and start it because uh i think it's
relatively easy to edit the pitch
on there it would be interesting
i wonder if we have enough content for
our videos to pull together a
a quick video of our other snippets from
our other discussions that sounds like a
lot of work but
it might be interesting to show that
there's lots of people
already kind of resonating with this
idea
get some with mark and i think it'll be
easier
once we have the prototype online we can
actually start to show we could even
have like a five minute hey here's
what the current version does and go
through it
and then just take that snippet out and
be like hey here's what we're building
is
this thing
so are you suggesting that we wait for
um or that we that i spend the time
building
a visual prototype first or i i think if
we
if we just write out a pitch on what one
tip
yeah i mean i think any writing that you
wanted to
do for that would still help we still
need it
but i think as the prototype actually
comes online that's going to make
that content easier to make like the
video
the you know the visual content showing
here's what it could look like
because i think that's an important part
to a a control
like that is it like when matuche was
explaining it it was very conceptual
it was like hey you've got this table
and then this and then you can set the
values
and it didn't really click for me until
i saw the mock-up he had made i'm like
oh
okay i see yeah i'm thinking more of
people describing the problem they want
to solve
so in our meetings on taking some of the
video clips from the meetings on food
saying
people saying i would like to have a
system where i could know what
um what companies don't have slavery
in their process right and and and some
of your stuff i drew about
you know you want to know what
politicians agree with you and actually
pass legislation that agrees with you
and doesn't just give you lip service
which
i don't know if you said it that way but
take those
stupid snippets as a way rather than
just a a wall of text on
anything i guess go for me i guess is it
i don't know if
i think that there are a lot like the
other funding platforms where it's good
to have a video
or is it mostly text i think it's always
good to have
a video yeah but um i was going to say
you already have some
prizes lined up you can come to a
together tech board meeting
online you're welcome to come to the
round table oh wait those things are
open no matter what but if we give them
away as prizes
right people might might show up you're
welcome to be on the board
together you got to show up for 10 weeks
in a row before that but
also that in our one-on-one time right
you can have someone
pick apart your utopian idea or
next steps in their attack anyway
yeah i think that having a crowdfunding
campaign well
be interesting i'm very willing to share
it i don't know
and you're willing i'm what's the word
you're more than welcome to use all
videos that are on
the together tech website and mine that
are on from solution raising
if there is someone who can edit that
video together
yeah on behalf of the project yeah
it's just a matter of time like
everything right now
yeah i guess i've created a campaign for
my brother's project
you'll be the go-to person for campaigns
from now on
because he didn't have enough on your
plate be the tech person the campaign
person
well i'll just link him to gofundme here
you go figure it out
so yeah i guess that's all the topics i
had
well we can i mean if you guys are done
the open source versus closed source
conversation um
i guess workshopping my workshop might
help
especially from people who i don't think
it actually
would at first glance appeal to um
as with all of my projects like just
come experience it and then you'll see
if it works for you
um something that
because i think it's actually more
powerful to come together and
crowdsource your solutions
there's an energy there's a like
that's not a god the universe that shows
up in the room where it's like how did
the right person show up and have the
exact answer there
but that's a side that's kind of that
that'll either be there or it won't be
there i can't make it be there
that
it's actually better than having
coaching like there's a
coaching is like a billion dollar
industry but having someone say they're
the expert on your health they're the
expert on finances they're the expert on
whatever they're the expert on even
though they all contradict each other
there's something very different that
happens when it's peer-to-peer
because then it's like right you could
be a financial expert but i'm not going
to take you at your word unless you
like you have to say it amongst other
people that don't think you're an expert
as well
and that's a different quality than
having someone um
that you've paid give you the answers to
your health to your finances to whatever
it is
so how i guess the question is what
how would i get you guys to come try
crowd sourcing your health or your
relationships
or your purpose your what you're doing
the hobbies the activity the verbs well
so it's a course so
you kind of have to go through all of
the
um sections so that is part of what so
the wish obstacle is the first one that
it can be anything
right so it's not tailor-made uh i could
make a
course on health of course on
relationships of course on
the individual pieces so that they are
more tailor-made or
that life structure right one on like
one week's focused on relationship
because you're just sharing what you've
what you you know a solution raising
where you are where you'd like to be
what's stopping you how can we help you
get there and
figuring out together how to best do
that
so the only thing i i think when i hear
that is that
i feel i i'd feel a bit overwhelmed
working on
all of that stuff with even within like
a a month or a couple months
um there are some parts of my life where
i have on uh on
hold or i've done enough research that
i'm not looking for additional
um information so like my health i've
got some plans i'm working on and i just
it
i just need to implement i just need to
get off my button exercise and
eat the foods that i have planned um
and like relationships and stuff so i i
guess i i only really want to work on
one two those things now
i think if if i if i knew i had
like if there were like five sessions i
knew that three of them i would get
value out of i'm happy to just
support other people um
and and trying to solve their problems
uh as a
as a part of getting the value of having
them help me solve mine
um but just as long as i don't have to
share in all of them
uh so that's that's that would be my
concern with doing it i guess
yeah thank you because making that clear
is very important because that is part
of it is
like right but then you can offer
something during the health week like
the more you have your together
the better you can offer and at the same
time not being the expert right being
someone who this has worked for
keto has worked for me i have that to
offer someone else right it's very
different than
keto works for everybody right
although that's what i would think but i
won't say that
but it's fine it's somewhat fine to say
that when someone's not paying you for
your authority
and it's instead like i think it works
for everyone the vegans there too being
like
actually you know right we'll just be
the right people
at the right time yeah yeah being able
to
advice like that is really helpful also
when it's tailored to the person
right because if i'm
the generic information on like how i
managed and found success in my diet
needs to be customized to be useful to
people
so it you know having a little bit of
time to just give them some tips that
apply specifically to them
i think would would be more valuable
than a generic
article
so the overarching theme to what i am
creating
is from the barbara cheer ted talk where
she says
like all of life is here to make you do
what you don't want to do
like what you have to do we're here to
make you do what you want to do
right so it's like you already know what
you're supposed to do for your health
what's the next step you could put into
place right like like how do we
including i don't want to share right
that's perfectly fine i don't want to
share
i'm not this isn't the area i'm looking
to get help in i'm good
is absolutely valid right that's part of
an invitation to share is also an
invitation that you are allowed to pass
and not share
um did i and
so you think it's better to have one
just health
just this just that and people because
then i have to fill that many courses
like if that's part of the broad
the broadness is having
something will speak to you right
there's one area of that that isn't
working for you that you're going to
want to come and be part of and yes then
we're focusing on other people's issues
during
the weeks that they're having let me
throw an idea that you've probably
already considered but even if it was
just
just six weeks and didn't have any
specific topics
and you can either like bring up the
same topic saying hey so
you know this is the advice i got last
week so here's the next kind of obstacle
i'm hitting in this goal um
and then people can focus on whatever
they want and just give a number
um with some sort of commitment
have you considered that or was there a
something that that misses that the
topics you think kind of
helps with part of it is
it's the topics help you
focus on it like it's like if i ask you
what's working in your life what's
what does your life currently look like
what would you love it to look like
what's stopping you
that is which obstacle but it's too
broad and our brains are like
life's good i don't know the world's
falling apart there's a pandemic like
it's
it's too much whereas it's like okay
what is your health like
and yes you can focus on mental you can
focus on physical you can focus on
emotional or
spiritual like what is your version it's
already gonna be that
because if you're really hurting in
relationships you're gonna bring
relationships into health
right that that's your obstacle so
when you work on any area you're
actually working on every area but
having one area to focus on
helps your brain like it helps
if that makes sense yeah you're right i
mean narrowing things down does
works better for human brains uh
i wonder if maybe it was posted as a
prompt
so people and just give the role hey you
know if you wanna if you wanna
deviate from this prompt for this
meeting that's fine
um or or have some open ones
mixed in with there and yeah i don't
know those those are some
some ideas i do think you're right you
do need prompts and i
and having it broken down is good
um i i just don't
know how i'd have to look at your list
to see how many of those i would have
something i would want to actually share
and i'm wondering if
people would still do it if they had
just one looked good like if you did
project and i'd
big question about reason score although
now that i have this time with you
guys every week i don't even have a need
there um
so uh although i could save it up and
use it in that in a way to um
yeah experiment with your your idea
and this is part of like we have this
space for our projects this is about our
projects
and then yes well you're gonna have to
do all the interpersonal work
we're unique i don't think most people
in the world have a project that is
something that's like their passion and
their purpose
this is a way to get them there but
through the back door right like omni
win works for you too
like getting better health we can do
that more together
getting better access to resources and
relationships
how do you define that and then how do
we together get you
closer no one's handing it to you right
no one's like great here's your that's
actually which obstacle a little bit is
someone handed you your wish over top of
your obstacle right helping you overcome
that
um but how do we crowdsource our lives
together
right so that's also the idea of it
being a very broad one
is you're somewhat designing your life
through it right what would your
relationships look like
what would your health look like what
would your what would you be doing with
your time in your perfect world
giving you a bit of a roadmap if you've
never thought about those things
and seeing the power in the collective
right that even if you didn't get your
problem solved you saw someone else get
their problem solved at like the perfect
time that they showed up and someone was
like hey it's exactly what they needed
to be introduced to keto
and it worked for them over the six
weeks yeah yeah it's interesting because
i mean we could all use a little
improvement in most of those areas um
certainly not perfect in any one
and i feel like i also need to put in
because everything i do is very
different than this this is not recorded
and made public to youtube
that's a good point yeah this is assume
you're in your
your your tiny group of people and
that's one of the iterations i'm not 100
sure on
um whether you're you're meeting with
the same people
every time the same three people or
whether it's let's say the same
12 50 50 people but it's mixed around
every week right so that you have a
fresh a fresh group of people my guess
is we'll try both
and see what works for some people one
will work and for some people the other
will work
yeah i think they'll be great there i
think there could be some synergies in
in having a recurring group for a period
of time but there is also
a center there is also a value in
in fresh meat
uh so yeah either like a batch
you know if this is an ongoing thing
which i don't think you've kind of said
it is but
yeah to have
three weeks or or maybe just like a few
people are coming in and out
each time uh
so you'd have mixed cohorts anyways
i don't know i don't need to make your
system more complex right now but
yeah maybe i don't need help with that
i'm pretty good at making it live
simply and you'll be able to experiment
with all that so yeah you don't
need to decide that now and in the first
batch you're not
you're not going to have enough people
to worry about that probably
right yeah and it is it's about making
something that
if if this wasn't enjoyable and there's
something that would make it enjoyable
it's our thing to make better
right yeah right it's like it has to be
this way
yeah so yeah i guess i guess a question
to how flexible you are
in each meeting that if i don't have if
i can't think of any way to phrase
needing and or benefiting from an
improvement to that thing because
sometimes i
i just don't even want to think about
that area of my life at the moment
is it okay to share something else or is
it better to just be silent and
try and provide value yeah and that's a
good
i mean i know in solution raising
sometimes they get completely off topic
that's exactly how they're supposed to
go like that's part of the
being in the moment and playing with it
and playing with like there's a human
being in front of you
that has a crisis or doesn't and just
brought up a random other thing it
usually adds to it
as opposed to taking it away but it's
about the other participants right if
you show up
wanting to talk about health and someone
side tracks it to relationships
does that work for more or less people
yeah and that's part of like right if
you're someone who needs it to be
structured like no no we're talking
about health because i signed up for
health
there's a slightly more rigid one for
you right like it's like right that's
that's where when we grow there can be
more diversity
in ways than it has to be so it works
for more people but
i'm very open so it's supposed to happen
as it hope happens
within reason
i've been hugging the time i don't know
if hatred has any thoughts or if he's
busy working away at something else
right now
[Laughter]
no i've just been listening
i'm not having dad i think that's a
valuable experiment julie so
we look forward to participating i think
it's something to get people into game b
that aren't game b
already and that's actually my opposite
issue is i'm like like this mlm
structure is about getting people in
game b retired from game a to game b
like people who are already in this
space they don't necessarily even need
this
this you know course but showcasing to
the
like it's a bit of a strange thing
because it's kind of bypassing that it's
like oh these people don't need that
but i want it to appeal to them so
there's some of the first people in
so that if anyone's getting retired it's
them but
and and creating this in a way that that
makes sense right if it's my thing
and then at the end of it i'm asking you
to bring your friends to the next one
right did this i want to know if you got
something under it if you could didn't
get something out of it how could you
get something out of it
and is it good enough to invite your
friends to right
is it something that you got enough
benefit it was free right
do you want more and more people here
that leads into something that is right
a month so we can get all of those
things all the things we created
together
in the health and the relationships in
some of them are just going to emerge
naturally right it's going to be the
right person at the right time
other ones are going to need a bigger
structure right if you can't afford your
insulin every month
that's maybe a more systemic problem
that
we could deal with with ten thousand
people and a hundred thousand dollars we
can't deal with it necessarily with
one person yeah and i
i still you know there's too many things
i want to accomplish but
a co-learning
platform where
it's not even the code learning part but
some place where you can go and
and this this comes into our writing
system to where you could be matched up
with content
in the areas that you want to grow and
then also a
a survey tool that lets you kind of
that walks you through that decision
process of what should i work on when
because
you know if you're having mental health
issues you you
you should probably tackle those first
before you just try and learn new skills
because you'll be so much more effective
in that order but then also if you have
nutrition
and mental health issues sometimes
handling the nutrition issues
will ease your mental health depending
on
of course the source but for some people
that does have a huge impact so maybe
you try some nutrition interventions
before you really focus on the mental
health if that doesn't work
so you know there are i think there are
some learnings there that could be
systematized in in a survey and a
process
very transparent like you can go in and
say why did the system suggest this
to me but i think that would be an
interesting
tool to a later
um following down your your same
path of value that and try and solve the
same problem
i love the going down the rabbit holes i
know what why does facebook keep
suggesting i need help with my mental
health this is
really what yeah
what is it about me that is
i tell you facebook got my number any
keto
treats i will click on there's these
cookies that are low carb cookies and
i'm like oh
and then you know low carb pizza
anything
they they finally figured me out i have
to say this mlm rabbit hole that i fell
down
and therefore i'm getting all of the
entrepreneurial ads
oh no both the bad ones but also the
good ones all of the ones that are five
days
free course creation i'm like oh i'm
never signing up for the paid ones
that's right you guys all have a free
version of the thing i need
and honestly it's perfect i just signed
up for another one that i can't remember
what it is
it was like how passionate what are you
gonna learn from this what are you i'm
like whatever i'm meant to
whenever i show up and it teaches me
like
right i'm not that excited for your free
course i don't know what to tell you
world changing it's like i'm gonna use
it to change the world so it is but
not in the way that you seem to be
selling it
yeah i'm using game a
against itself i'll learn marketing
i'll learn just not editing that doesn't
seem to be the thing that people are
offering in a five-day course
well like video editing yeah yeah
although honestly it's more executive
functioning it's like picking the parts
that need to get cut out not cut out
it's more that
like it's more i'm pretty sure i could
sit down and learn how to physically
edit a video just not edit a video
not make the actual decisions that can
put it together it's too much
yeah i'm just trying to think i mean i
follow several youtubers and some of
them talk about their process
um but i don't know if i could find
those videos again
because like you said they're not put
together in a course um
a free course there's lots of paid
courses
on that also do you think
that's something that your brain is made
for
what do you think you need that no
someone else needs to i'm very clear
the universe has not provided me with
any easy simple
free tools to learn in video editing
because a person is probably supposed to
do it
like i've learned to create thumbnails
the little things i could do just not
the big ones
this is really good uh you you do a
really good job with that
but yeah that that's yeah that's um i
mean i'm not saying i learned how to
create good thumbnails
just just thumbnails just not my
face it's my face caught in a frozen
motion with
attached to it because i never make a
neutral face it turns out
like ever that it captures
yeah no i have that same problem
oh i wouldn't have thought that about
you so that's good to know
maybe i'm just overly self-conscious and
see myself in photos
i found out today i can't smile um like
does that look happy
sort of looks kind of judgy i think i
think every
every face i have is judgey
jack nicholson i don't know i don't know
it's hilarious
that's where that's the thumbnail that
youtube's gonna pick for this right is
me doing this
uh yeah i was that's what i'm making we
were out for the first time the other uh
last night
uh at a restaurant on a patio uh social
distancing and so i was taking a picture
and i had to
take like three or four i didn't like
any of my smiles but it's probably just
not being too self-conscious
yeah i liked i saw the picture i thought
it was i wasn't like he's looking
judgy did you see my weird gang sign my
hand was like this
i was like what am i doing there
and i like i took three shots and my
wife goes well that one
i look best in the one with the hand
gang sign so so that's the one to share
anyways wait tmi running out all right
we have 10 more minutes let's talk about
more photographic
photographic needs
i only just found out this is part of
crowdfunding solutions there's like a
white powder on the zucchini leaves and
i thought it was part of the zucchini
but it's actually a fungus i was
supposed to take care of when it first
started i was like oh
oh it's still creating zucchini though
so i'm not quite understanding and i'm
like it's
zucchini is just fine it's only the leaf
still photosynthesizing
i don't know interesting
yeah i'd love to have a garden but i'd
also love to have someone else
take care of it
let's have a pre-made spot where
somebody just goes there and grows food
and then distributes it
some
or a farmer's store or anything like
that
i am thinking about putting an iv wall
in my new house but that's one of those
projects that i want to do and i never
actually get around to it so
we'll see
how do you like the idea of having other
people's information
oh that was yeah household emergency
uh so yeah i guess i will
um work on a pitch for this
and adria you probably have some pitches
for could you find me a snippet of text
like a sentence or two on how um
conferrati and or uh wikilections
would be using that piece
um just the phrasing it's probably just
the general description
of i can't think of anything
did i ever cover that in my webinars
i think you covered it every time
because apart the big piece is
seeing is it matching
trying to think of how you yeah i'm
trying to think how i would have phrased
that i mean
in general that's something where like i
think that part will probably
happen more naturally once the prototype
is out then we can do a quick like hey
here's how it works and that
five minute conversation will be chock
full of
different snippets and screenshots and
things that will
yeah i was just hoping to get some
funding to make the prototype
so and i think if you can't describe
an idea well enough without a prototype
it may not be
well not everything's that way something
part of it is
like i'm i would be describing
one implementation of the tool i'm less
attached to the idea of it being a tool
as opposed to just being an aspect of
the prototype and i think that's what
the pitch needs to be i think it needs
to be it can be used for this
and for that so really it's just the
snippet of what conferadi is and what
right that part of wikilection where you
get to rate
or see ratings of legislation right yeah
you can start to see like some of the
underlying where it came from and okay
here's how the legislation is rated
here's how they interacted here's
what's happening on that person's
profile because of it well yeah
although even just the one or two
sentences it says you can rate
politicians and you can see their
ratings
right it's really just one or two
sentences
which i could probably make up but i can
ask eric because my memory is not the
best
um he's been to the most solution
raisings besides me
that uh when we've come up with that
like which
topics we needed a rating system in
because it feels like it's definitely
one of the meta ones one of the ones
that comes up
quite regularly yeah yeah if y'all think
of any of the videos and
can shoot that to me then um i can look
and see if i want to edit any
chunks out but yeah i drew if you think
of anything just
shoot me a sentence or two sure yeah i
mean it
it's been like an ever pushed deadline
but i'm hoping to have
the new prototype online this weekend
and then
yeah we'll definitely see what what what
he has because that that may be
the the prototype i just don't know if
he
had the waiting and the visualizations
in there which
may or may not be important to explain
because it may just
maybe we don't even want to go in that
level of detail and just say
you will be able to we will be able to
rate
attributes and not even talk about well
rate attributes and then
and then just say we will match you with
ones that you align with
and not talk about how the weighting is
when you choose weights and all that
stuff just keep it simple right
yeah yeah so it might yeah it'll be
interesting let me know
um when that's out and we'll see if
that is the prototype we need because
he's obviously put a lot of
hard and efficient work into it
yeah i'm looking forward to seeing what
that looks like and then of course the
the next task is to fill it up with data
yeah
i could buy help with some of that
although you still want to start with
fictional um at this point for the
prototype i'm just
going for data that actually exists so i
sent him a list of like all the us
congress people and senators
um and then once we have that load and i
i've got the ids i'm gonna go find like
to start with i don't know four or five
pieces of legislation that people have
have voted on and that like
i can think of some form of like oh okay
that's kind of either for or against
environmentalism or
whatever it is like at a broad level um
and then it's just adding more and more
legislation over time
and better ways to visualize it in that
whole thing
i guess we're out of time yeah
or almost any closing thoughts
nope we're meeting for together attack
next week
we're on friday and then this on
saturday again next week as
for all weeks so bring your this is
even more open than our friday session
which feels weird when people just pop
into that one
which make it a little more closed-ish
and then
this one like you have to have like
steve being there actually
made sense he's attended a lot of them
even though he doesn't want to speak
whatever he can attend and type in their
comments um
but it has been weird having someone
because it's like it's open anyway
this one is like bring your project
including different projects you and
you're looking for a project right come
say what you've been up to
we'll help you crowdsource solutions to
your project
you don't need to concentrate on your
different areas of life
can ignore them and just create game b
that's what we're all doing
it's perfect perfect who needs
relationships in health
when you've got game b but yeah so we
have this next week and then friday
we'll
be talking about the mission more
specifically than we did this last week
all right goodbye youtube and facebook
have a good week